<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>

    <metadata>
        <title>Invincible</title>
        <creator>ROBERT KIRKMAN (CO-CREATOR, WRITER, LETTERER)Cory Walker( Co-Creator, Artist) Billl
            Crabtree(Colorist)</creator>
        <publisher>Jim Valentino(ImageComics)</publisher>
        <date>Apri 2003</date>
        <language>english</language>
        <issue n="3">Compendium 1</issue>
        <link>https://archive.org/details/invincible-compendiums/Invincible%2C%20Vol.%201/page/n51/mode/2up</link>
    </metadata>

    <comic>
        <page n="52">
            <panel p="1">
                <caption speaker="Mayor?">WE ARE CURRENTLY WORKING WITH THE AUTHORITIES TO GlVE THEM
                    ALL THE INFORMATION WE CAN IN ORDER TO HELP THEM LOCATE THE MISSING STUDENTS.
                    .</caption>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mayor">I MUST STRESS TO YOU ALL THAT THIS IS NOT A REASON TO
                    PANIC. THE THREE MISSING STUDENTS, THOUGH REPORTED MISSING ON DIFFERENT DAYS,
                    DID KNOW EACH OTHER. IT'S POSSIBLE THIS WAS PLANNED BY THEM AND NO FOUL PLAY HAS
                    TAKEN PLACE. STILL, WE CALLED THIS SCHOOL MEETING SO THAT THE RUMORS WOULDN'T
                    OVERWHELM THE TRUTH. YOU KNOW WHAT WE KNOW. JUST TO BE SAFE TRY NOT TO GO
                    ANYWHERE ALONE, AND PLEASE REPORT ANYTHING SUSPICIOUS TO EITHER ME OR ANY OF THE
                    OTHER PEOPLE YOU SEE HERE BESIDES ME.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mayor">IF WE'RE LUCKY, THE MISSING STUDENTS WILL SHOW UP AND
                    EVERYTHING WILL GO BACK TO NORMAL, BUT UNTIL THEN KEEP YOUR EARS OPEN. IF ANY OF
                    YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS, I'LL BE IN MY OFFICE IN ABOUT FIFTEEN MINUTES AND MORE
                    THAN LIKELY FOR THE REST OF THE DAY. YOU CAN ALL GO BACK TO CLASS NOW. JUST GO
                    ON TO FOURTH PERIOD FROM HERE. PEOPLE WHO ARE ON FIRST LUNCH PERIOD CAN GO ON TO
                    THE CAFETERIA. THE BELL WILL RING IN SEVEN MINUTES, PLEASE BE WHERE YOU'RE
                    SUPPOSED TO BE BY THEN.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="53">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">EVERYONE'S THINKING IT... AND I'M GOING TO BE THE GUY TO
                    SAY IT. WHATEVER HAPPENED... COULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED TO A NICER BUNCH OF
                    GUYS.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">JESUS, MARK! THAT'S A PRETTY MEAN THING TO SAY! I TALKED TO
                    TODD A FEW TIMES... I MEAN, I CAN'T SPEAK FOR THE OTHER TWO BUT HE AT LEAST
                    SEEMED NICE.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">YOU'RE TOTALLY CLUELESS! WHY DO YOU THINK TODD JEFFERSON
                    WOULD BE NICE TO YOU? OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD... I THINK IT MAY HAVE SOMETHING TO
                    DO WITH YOU BEING AN EXTREMELY ATTRACTIVE GIRL.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">YOU KNOW I'M DATING REX, RIGHT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WHOA, WHOA! THAT'S NOT WHERE I WAS GOING WITH THAT AT ALL!
                    ... HEH.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">RIIIGHT. SO, ARE YOU ON YOUR WAY TO THE CAFETERIA TOO, OR
                    ARE YOU JUST WALKING WITH ME?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WELL, I GUESS WE HAVE THE SAME LUNCH PERIOD, TOO. I CAN'T
                    BELIEVE WE HADN'T MET BEFORE LAST MONTH.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="54">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">IS THIS SEAT TAKEN?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">NOT AT ALL. HAVE AT IT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SORRY IF I MADE IT WEIRD BACK THERE. I JUST WANTED TO MAKE
                    SURE YOU DIDN'T THINK--</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT. IT DOESN'T NEED TO BE BROUGHT UP
                    AGAIN.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <action>Mark and Eve sit in silence.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <action>Mark and Eve sit in silence.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SO... SURE IS FUN BEING A SUPER-HERO, ISN'T IT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">DID YOU HEAR THERE WAS ANOTHER MALL BOMBING? ROBOT IS TRYING
                    TO FIGURE OUT WHO'S BEHIND THEM, BUT THE BOMBS ARE SO POWERFUL THEY ARE
                    DISINTEGRATING ALL THE EVIDENCE AT THE SCENE.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="8">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">ANOTHER BOMBING? THAT'S TWO IN LESS THAN THREE
                    WEEKS.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="55">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">IF YOU WANT TO SWING BY THE... "SECRET LAIR" (OR WHATEVER
                    THE BOYS CALL IT) AFTER SCHOOL TODAY, I'M SURE ROBOT WOULD BE GLAD TO SEE YOU.
                    YOU NEVER DID GET BACK TO HIM ON WHETHER OR NOT YOU WERE GOING TO JOIN THE
                    TEAM.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN MAKE IT. I'VE GOT TO WORK
                    TONIGHT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">YOU STILL WORK AT THE BURGER MART? ISN'T YOUR DAD A
                    SEMI-FAMOUS NOVELIST?!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WELL.. YEAH, I MEAN... IT'S NOT LIKE I NEED THE MONEY, HE
                    MAKES ME WORK THERE BECAUSE HE THINKS IT BUILDS CHARACTER.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Eve">WEIRD. WELL, I'VE GOT TO GET TO CLASS. SEE YOU
                    AROUND.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">LATER.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="William">SO, THE RUMORS ARE TRUE. YOU GUYS ARE GOING
                    OUT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">OH. HEY, WILLIAM... GOING OUT WHERE?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="William">DON'T PLAY DUMB WITH ME. YOU TWO ARE AN ITEM, BOYFRIEND
                    AND GIRLFRIEND, AND ALL THE PERKS THAT COME WITH IT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">TRUST ME. SHE'S NOT MY GIRLFRIEND.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="56">
            <panel p="1">
                <action>The sign outside for Burger Mart is shown.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <action>Mark is shown in the kicthen looking distressed.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Dan">GRAYSON! FRIES! WE GOT CUSTOMERS WAITING!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">COMING RIGHT UP, SIR!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Dan">COMING RIGHT UP? DO YOU REALIZE HOW LONG OUR CUSTOMERS HAVE
                    BEEN WAITING?! DON'T YOU KNOW THAT WAITING CUSTOMERS AREN'T HAPPY
                    CUSTOMERS?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">NO... I GUESS NOT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="57">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Dan">YOU GUESS?!??! WELL, YOU BETTER HOPE COME FRIDAY THAT I
                    GUESS THAT YOU SHOULD GET PAID! NOW, GO TAKE OUT THE TRASH. I'LL FINISH THE
                    FRIES!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">YOU KNOW WHAT? I THINK I'LL JUST QUIT INSTEAD!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">JERK!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <action>Mark is standing outside of Burger Mart after quitting.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">DAD'S GOING TO KILL ME.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="58">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">BOY, THAT CASSEROLE SURE WAS GOOD, MOM.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">ABSOLUTELY, HON'. YOU REALLY OUTDID YOURSELF
                    TONIGHT.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Debbie">THANKS, BUT YOU'RE BOTH STILL GOING TO HAVE TO DO THE
                    DISHES.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">CURSES... FOILED AGAIN.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">SO, HOW WAS WORK TODAY?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">OH! FINE! DO YOU WANT TO WASH OR RINSE!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">OH, I'LL BE WASHING, TONIGHT. HOW MANY DISHES DID I HAVE
                    TO HAND BACK TO YOU LAST NIGHT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">I WAS THINKING... NOW THAT YOU'RE AN ACTIVE SUPER-HERO,
                    YOU'VE GOT MORE IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO THAN FLIP BURGERS. I DON'T SEE ANY REASON
                    WHY YOU CAN'T JUST QUIT. IT'S NOT LIKE YOU EVER REALLY NEEDED THE
                    MONEY.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I THINK I COULD MANAGE THAT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="59">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">HEY MARK. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I'M JUSTGETTING READY TО GO OUT ON PATROL. I FIGURED I'D
                    TAKE A STROLL AROUND THE CITY BY AIR AND MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S ON THE UP AND
                    UP. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">YOU MND IF I TAG ALONG? I THINK WE'RE ABOUT DUE FORA
                    TEAM-UP.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">THAT WOULD BE GREAT!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">HEH. YOU SAID "TEAM-UP."</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="60">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">YOU KNOW, FROM ALL INDICATIONS YOU'RE NOT DOING TOO BAD.
                    ESPECIALLY FOR BEING AS NEW TO THIS AS YOU ARE.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">THANKS, DAD. I--HUH?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">SORRY ABOUT THAT. THERE WASSA CHEMICAL FIRE OVER AT THE
                    UNIVERSITY'S SCIENCE LAB.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">ANYWAY, AS I WAS SAYING... YOU'VE DONE A LOT OF GOOD THESE
                    PAST THREE MONTHS. TO BE QUITE HONEST, I'M IMPRESSED. </dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="61">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">THAT REALLY MEANS A LOT COMING FROM YOU, DAD.
                    THANKS.</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">DON'T THANK ME, SON. JUST KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK.
                </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">LOOK OUT DAD, THAT DAM IS ABOUT TO-- </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SHOW OFF.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">YOU WANT TO GRAB SOME LUNCH?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SURE.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="62">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SO... IS THAT GOING TO COME NATURALLY OR AM I GOING TO HAVE
                    TO PRACTICE? I MEAN, I COULD BARELY KEEP UP WITH YOU ON THE WAY HERE! </dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">AS YOU GET OLDER AND YOUR POWERS INCREASE, YOU SHOULD BE
                    ABLE TO FLY FASTER. TO BE HONEST, I DON'T KNOW HOW ALL THIS IS GOING TO WORK.
                    YOU MAY NEVER GET AS POWERFUL AS ME. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I GUESS I COULDN'T COMPLAIN IF THEY NEVER INCREASED AT
                    ALL.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">YEAH, AND ANOTHER THING IS THAT YOU DON'T EVEN REALLY KNOW
                    HOW TO USE THE POWERS YOU HAVE, YET. JUST WAIT UNTIL-- HOLD ON... </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">OH, JEEZ!! I'LL BE BACK IN A MINUTE!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <action>Mark is sitting and eating.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">I GOING TO NEED YOUR HELP ON THIS ONE </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <action>Mark and Nolan have flown away.</action>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="63">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WHOA!</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="64">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">NO TIME FOR THAT, SON! LET'S HELP THESE BOYS OUT!
                </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I'LL DO WHAT I CAN!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">THAT'S THE SPIRIT!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SURE ARE A LOT OF THESE GUYS!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">NO KIDDING! THERE SEEMS TO BE AN ENDLESS STREAM OF THEM
                    COMING OUT OF THAT PORTAL.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="65">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WELL, YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY NOT FROM AROUND HERE. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">LET ME HELP YOU FIND YOUR WAY HOME.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">I THINK WE'RE DEALING WITH SOME SORT OF OTHER-DIMENSIONAL
                    ARMY HERE. I DON'T RECOGNIZE THESE THINGS AT ALL. WHICH MEANS THEY COULD HAVE AN
                    ENTIRE UNIVERSE WORTH OF SOLDIERS READY TO SPILL OUT OF THAT THING! WE'VE GOT TO
                    GET THEM BACK IN THAT PORTAL AND FIGURE OUT A WAY TO CLOSE THAT THING
                    FAST!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">ANY IDEAS?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">NOT YET... NO.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="66">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WAIT A SECOND...</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">...IS IT JUST ME, OR ARE THESE GUYS GETTING SLOWER?
                </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">NOW THAT YOu MENTION IT THIS SEEMS TO BE GETTING EASIER.
                </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">JEEZ, DAD! THIS GUY IS AGING BY THE MINUTE!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">TIME MUST WORK DIFFERENTLY IN THEIR DIMENSION. THEY'RE
                    STARTING TO DROP LIKE FLIES!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">YEAH, AND IF THERE WEREN'T SO MANY OF THEM... WE'D BE
                    WINNING THIS BATTLE! </dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="67">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">WE'RE NOT DEFEATED YET! </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">RAARGH!!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">GET OFF MY PLANET!</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="68">
            <panel p="1">
                <action>The fight is now over.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">DAD?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">IT'S OKAY DAD. THEY'RE LEAVING. IT'S OVER.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">...YOU'RE RIGHT. LET'S GO.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="69">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">SO... DOES THAT HAPPEN OFTEN? </dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">THANKFULLY, NO. THAT WAS NOT A PLEASANT EXPERIENCE.
                </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">IF ANOTHER COUPLE OF SECONDS HAD GONE BY BEFORE WE
                    DISCOVERED THEIR ACCELERATED AGING I WOULD HAVE CALLED IN THE GUARDIANS OF THE
                    GLOBE, OR MEGAFORCE... OR BOTH. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WOW.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">I GUESS I DIDN'T REALLY NOTICE HOW BAD IT GOT. </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">WELL... WE MADE IT THROUGH. DON'T DWELL ON IT. LET'S JUST
                    WORRY ABOUT GETTING HOME WITHOUT RUNNING INTO ANY MORE TROUBLE. WE'RE ALMOST
                    THERE, AND I'LL BET YOUR MOM'S ALMOST DONE WITH--</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">LAKESIDE MALL. TRY TO KEEP UP.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="70">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">CRAP. WHAT IS IT?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">NO TIME.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <action>Mark is flying.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <action>Nolan is ahead of Mark</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">CRAP!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <action>Nolan is even further ahead</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <action>Mark is headed towards the ground</action>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="71">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">WHAT'S GOING ON?</dialogue>
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">WAKE UP! WAKE UP!! WHAT? WH--WHAАТ ARE YOU
                    DOING?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">QUICKLY! TELL ME WHO DID THIS TO YOU!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Rick">D--DID WHAT?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <action>Nolan looks scared or confused.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <action>Nolan throws Rick through the roof.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <action>Rick explodes.</action>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="72">
            <panel p="1">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">THAT WAS ONE OF THE MISSING STUDENTS FROM MY SCHOOL!
                </dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">BUT THAT WOULD MEAN--</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Nolan">HUH?</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">DAD!!</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <action>Mark is staring off into space.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="6">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">DANG IT.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="7">
                <action>Mark flys away.</action>
            </panel>
        </page>
        <page n="73">
            <panel p="1">
                <action>Mark gets home.</action>
            </panel>
            <panel p="2">
                <dialogue speaker="Debbie">I GUESS I CAN LOOK FORWARD TO YOU BOTH BEING LATE FROM
                    NOM ON...</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="3">
                <dialogue speaker="Mark">ACTUALLY... DAD WAS SUCKED INTО А PORTAL ABOUT FIFTEEN
                    MINUTES AGO, I DON'T THINK HE'LL BE HOME TONIGHT. IT WAS SOME ALIENS WE FOUGHT
                    EARLIER TODAY... I'M SURE HE'S FINE.</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="4">
                <dialogue speaker="Debbie">...</dialogue>
            </panel>
            <panel p="5">
                <dialogue speaker="Debbie">WELL, THAT'S MORE PORK CHOPS FOR US.</dialogue>
            </panel>
        </page>
    </comic>




</xml>
